<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<newsfeed>

<post id="1"><title>Fashion thing</title><user>vishal</user><date>15-04-2020</date><tags>political;fashion</tags><likes>1</likes><content>Political influences certainly play a major role in influencing Fashion. Many politicians become fashion symbols. Notable examples are First Lady Jacqueline Kennedy and Princess Diana. Also, political revolutions make a huge impact on the Fashion trend. For example, in 1960’s America, liberal clothing styles became popular among the younger generation. This was due to the Liberal revolution.

Another significant factor which influences Fashion trend is technology. There certainly has been a rapid growth of technology in the Fashion industry. For example, wearable technology has become a popular Fashion trend. Furthermore, 3D printing technology and the internet have also made an impact on Fashion.

Social influences are probably the strongest influences on the Fashion trend. Many music stars strongly influence Fashion choice. For example, wearing hoodies became famous due to rap musicians. Furthermore, movie and television actors create a big impact on Fashion. Many youngsters love to emulate the Fashion sense of their favourite celebrity.</content><comments>I did not like it</comments></post><post id="2"><title>TRAVELLLL!</title><user>vishal</user><date>15-04-2020</date><tags>Travel;Fitness</tags><likes>2</likes><content>There is nothing quite like traveling, like seeing a new place for the first time or returning to a favorite one. People of all ages, from all around the world, go to foreign places for different reasons – mainly, for work, family, and leisure. Whether by plane, train, ship or by automobile, traveling is generally a pleasurable experience, at least for the people who can financially afford comfortable and safe methods of travel. But it has more benefits than satisfying one’s need to make money, like, for example, to see loved ones and enjoy oneself on vacation. There are other benefits of traveling worth mentioning and trying out</content><comments>Amazing</comments></post><post id="3"><title>Footballlllllllllllll</title><user>vishal</user><date>15-04-2020</date><tags>Fitness;Sports</tags><likes>3</likes><content>Football is a game that millions of people around the world play and love. It can be called a universal game because every small and big nation plays it.

Moreover, it’s a great relaxer, stress reliever, teacher of discipline and teamwork. Apart from that, it keeps the body and mind fit and healthy. It’s a team game that makes it a more enjoyable game as it teaches people the importance of sportsmanship. Leadership, and unity.</content><comments>Worst one yet</comments></post><post id="4"><title>Investment Banking</title><user>sparsha</user><date>15-04-2020</date><tags>finance</tags><likes>13</likes><content>It is a financial intermediary that specializes primarily in selling securities and underwriting the issuance of new equity shares to raise capital funds. This is different from a commercial bank, which specializes in deposits and commercial loans. It assists individuals, corporations, and governments in raising financial capital by underwriting or acting as the client’s agent in the issuance of securities. An investment bank may also assist companies involved in mergers and acquisitions (M</content><comments>Amazing story</comments></post><post id="5"><title>Fashion and Travel experience</title><user>sparsha</user><date>15-04-2020</date><tags>Travel;fashion</tags><likes>5</likes><content>Travelling to Paris is what got me into Fashion.
Everyone who knows me knows that my passion for life and goals must be consistent with fashion. If I can do everything in this world, I would like to be a type of designer, or at least a designer in this industry. In terms of clothing and style, it is easy to become one of the easiest things that I am good at. Fashion is an art form that allows you to express your perception of style anyway. For me, I do not think anyone has the right to judge this. Styles are not always easy, but as with all other time and customs, it is still a work in progress. 

Entering the world of fashion is a purely personal choice. In fact, art is my passion and fashion, a medium to express myself as an artist. Art is part of me, I do not remember when it was not. The ability to enhance personal personality, express myself, raise confidence, and show (including clothing and accessories) to provide acceptance that I am a fashion designer has fascinated me. Being able to do this for one person is another part of why I am a fashion designer.</content><comments>Disappointed</comments></post></newsfeed>
